Hey, Davidson, congratulations. Uh, how
would you describe to Bills fans the
type of player and the type of mindset
you bring to a team?
>> Um, I'm getting you're getting a player
that's built for Buffalo, built for the
Bills mouth. You're getting a nasty,
edgy player who sets the tone in the
secondary. Um, who's who's um ultra
aggressive and and and just a competitor
who who lives for the matchup outside.
Just just I live for for me versus him.
>> Thank you. Appreciate it.
>> Mookie,
you want to know?
>> I think we got Hey, Davidson. Uh, I
think I got unmuted here. My name is Sal
from WGR radio in Buffalo. How are you?
>> I'm good. How are you?
>> Good. Congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Um, it says your says Davidson. That's
what you go by, but I'm seeing that's
that's actually your middle name. Can
you say your full name for us and how to
pronounce it all?
Davidsona.
>> Yes. I like a the letter I
>> David.
And
>> my first name means you can't argue with
God.
>> Thank you for that. I appreciate it. I'm
going to go back and relisten about 10
times before I try to get it right
again. Just so you know. Thank you. I
appreciate David. But you do prefer to
be called Davidson, right? We just want
to make sure here.
Everybody calls me I go by IGB.
>> IGB. Okay.
>> And and and so that's okay with the
media calling you IGB. You okay with
that? You prefer that?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay, great. Thank you. Um I'm
interested in, you know, you took some
penalties a couple years ago. They
tailored off a little bit last year, but
how did you kind of correct that? You
know, what's your thought on, you know,
how that's evolved for you over the last
couple of years?
>> Yeah, that's the thing. Like I'm always
trying to get better and improve my
game. So like obviously that was
something that I needed to improve on my
game that was kind of holding me back a
little bit. So I just made that emphasis
a focus point in the offseason with my
coaches at Ohio State just watching the
film and just seeing a lot of the
situations I was in wasn't that I was
necessarily beat. I was in great
position a lot of times just needed to
relax and play with poise at the top of
the route. Like a lot of those PI should
have been PBUS and interceptions should
have been ball production.
>> Uh as you can see by my name I'm also a
Sopranos fan. Uh, what do you what what
got you into the TV show? I'm reading
your bio. And do you have a favorite
episode?
>> What got me into the TV show? I mean,
I'm from Jersey, so like just
growing up.
>> My favorite episode,
I want to say when Tony is trying to
kill that guy on the boat. I don't want
to say his name.
>> Okay. Yeah, you got it.
>> Yeah, I can't say his name. Yeah, his
name's
>> I understand. Hey, good man. You're
already like,
>> "Yeah,
>> you got this media thing down. You're on
a Zoom call. I get it. Everybody's going
to hear this. I know what you mean. I I
appreciate that."
>> Yeah,
>> that's Hey, let's end on that. That's
really cool. Thanks, IGB.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Yeah, that that was definitely a great
scene. IBG Muki Hawkins, Waffle Sports,
congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
>> So, uh, just tell us what was your
reaction when you saw Buffalo on the
caller ID?
>> It just made sense. like you know with
this whole like process you can't like
you know you you you know a lot of
people in the process you make good
connections but you never know you know
it's a business at the end of the day
but like I know when I went to Buffalo I
put my best foot forward I felt very
connected with the guys just hanging out
with Hancock and and Max Haristston and
just all the boys um strong just sitting
at the that was the first time I sat at
the table with some guys I'm like dang I
wouldn't be mad if I had to be with boys
every day like it wouldn't be the worst
thing so like and I and I um had a hit
me in with the I just like the people in
the building. They're just authentic.
So, I just I wasn't surprised, but you
know, it's just nerve-wracking drafting.
>> Yeah, man. We know Buffalo kind of leans
heavily on the zone with match
principles. So, how did that align with
uh your strengths or your skill set?
>> Yeah, I think that's another thing in my
game like I feel like I have I have a
lot of I I I I would say I I have a lot
of areas to improve on and a lot of
areas in our weather. Like we played a
lot of zone at Ohio. I played a lot of I
play a lot of different defenses in
college. So, played a lot of zone at
Ohio State. I'm excited. I think I think
I'll prosper in this system.
>> Did you speak with Jordan Hancock at all
since you've been selected?
>> Um I he facetimed me. I didn't hear what
he said. He screaming at me. I was
screaming at him. But I spoke to him
though.
>> Right. That's enough said right there,
man. I appreciate the time and I'll see
you tomorrow.
>> Thank you.
>> Hey, IGB. This is Cath from the Buffalo
News. Congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Um, that sounds like a wonderful Zoom
call with Jordan. So excited to get you
here and hear more about it.
>> Um, but I was curious, Brandon Bean was
saying how you add a different element
to this defense. How would you describe
your game?
>> I would say like I'm a smart club. Like
I feel like like my teammates feed off
me. I set the tone. I play with passion.
I play with energy. Like every day I
don't take anything for granted. When
I'm on the football field, I turn it up.
I'm not just out there to be out there.
I don't I don't take advantage of the
days like.
>> And then just what has this draft
process been like for you? Like who are
you watching with? Where are you
watching from? What is the environment
been like?
>> In Union, New Jersey at my mother's
house surrounded by my closest friends
and my family. So meant the world to me.
>> Thanks and congrats again.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Hi IGB Matt Pino from Syracuse.com.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you so much.
Um, we were just talking to Brandon for
a few minutes and and he had mentioned
uh Jay Valive being somebody that's very
familiar with your game. What when you
had those conversations with him during
the draft process, what were some of the
things that you guys either connected on
or you felt like, you know, this would
be from a football perspective a great
fit?
>> Um, so I would say coach Valai, he
actually coached at Ruckers. You know,
I'm a Jersey kid, so like I knew I knew
all of the Ruckers coaches. I knew of
them and they knew of me. So he kind of
knows my background like just growing up
being in New Jersey just jersey tough
being from the concrete. Um I would say
we just connected cuz like he loves he
loves football and I love football too
and like he saw that
with the tools that I have at corner and
and his coaching he thinks that we'll
have a good partnership and I agree.
>> What is your I'm going to put you on the
spot. What's your favorite memory from
Ohio State?
>> That's easy. Winning a national
championship. But I also enjoyed beating
team up nerf. Not gonna lie. That felt
like a national championship, but it
wasn't.
>> Well, there's a couple of uh Michigan
folks in the media here. It's a little
bit They can't wait for you to get to
town.
>> I'll be I'll be waiting to see them,
too. All right. Thanks, IB. For sure.